https://www.premiumwp.com/privacy-policy/

We’re updating our Privacy Policy on May 25, 2018. Our new policy and current policy are both below.
This is our updated Privacy Policy which goes into effect on May 25, 2018.
Who We Are
PremiumWP provides WordPress news, information and resources and assists WordPress users find the best commercial (premium) WordPress themes, plugins and services.
Our website address is: https://www.premiumwp.com/
What Personal Data We Collect
The privacy and security of our site visitors is our highest priority and PremiumWP.com maintains privacy policies to protect your personal information.
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Email/Contact Forms
Customers that email us, or use any of the contact forms on our websites, will have their email address, IP address, and any data provided in the contact form or body of the email stored indefinitely. We do not use the information submitted through them for marketing purposes.
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. We use cookies across our sites to help identify and track visitors, their usage of our services, and their website access preferences. We describe the specific cookies used in the sections below. Visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using our websites, with the drawback that certain features may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded Content From Other Websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
We use Google Analytics for tracking visitors and aggregating information about the traffic to our websites. The Google Analytics privacy policy can be found here: https://policies.google.com/privacy. You can learn more about how to opt-out of tracking in Google Analytics here.
Who We Share Your Data With
We use third-party services on our site. The following is a list of possible cookies and data collected that may be shared when using PremiumWP. Please refer to each service’s privacy policy for more information on the exact types of data collected:
Google Analytics
Cloudflare
How Long We Retain Your Data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What Rights You Have Over Your Data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where We Send Your Data
We use Akismet on PremiumWP to help prevent spam. Visitor comments may be checked through this automated spam detection service.
How We Protect Your Data
The security and reliability of our service is our number one priority. Premium.com takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration, or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying data.
Policy Revisions
Any changes to the privacy policy will be promptly communicated on this website. Policy changes will not alter how we handle previously submitted personal information.
Contacting PremiumWP.com
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the terms and conditions, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, please contact us.
————-
This is the previous Privacy Policy which will be replaced on May 25, 2018.
The privacy and security of our site visitors is our highest priority. It is the policy of PremiumWP.com that personal information, such as your name, personal postal and email address, or personal telephone number is private and confidential. Because your privacy is important to us, PremiumWP.com maintains privacy policies to protect your personal information.
By using this site, you consent to the terms of our privacy policy for the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information for the purposes set out below. We do not collect, use or disclose your personal information for any purpose other than those identified below, except with your consent or as required by law.
Information we gather or track
(1) Site Activity Data
Each time a visitor comes to this website, our web server collects and logs certain information. These access logs are kept for a reasonable period of time. These logs include, but are not restricted to your machine’s TCP/IP address, your username (if applicable), date, time and files accessed. These logs also contain information about ‘referrer’ information if you clicked on an external link to a PremiumWP.com webpage. These logs are used solely for performance, site administration and security reviews. They are not sold or shared in any way to third party organizations.
(2) Cookies
Your browser offers “cookies” which — if you allow their use — store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to our site. Cookies assist us in tracking which of our offerings you like best. And when we make this function available in the future, cookies will enable us to customize our content according to your preferences. However, cookies tell us nothing about you personally unless you specifically give us additional information. This information is used solely to maintain your computer’s session to the PremiumWP.com server. This information is not shared or sold to third party organizations for any purpose.
Some of the banner ads displayed on PremiumWP.com are provided by outside companies. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our advertisers and we do not have access to this information.
Cookies in and of themselves do not contain any personally identifiable information about you.
(3) Personal Information
Personal information, such as your name, personal postal and email address, or personal telephone number is collected only when you voluntarily provide it. Such information is received when you send an email through the site or make some other specific contact, such as completing an online form.
Policy Revisions
Any changes to the privacy policy will be promptly communicated on this website. Policy changes will not alter how we handle previously submitted personal information.
Contacting PremiumWP.com
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the terms and conditions, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, please contact us.
Primary SidebarSubscribe to PremiumWP
Subscribe to PremiumWP and receive notifications of new posts by email.
Email Address
Subscribe
Footer WidgetsAbout PremiumWP PremiumWP was established in 2007 to assist WordPress users find the best commercial (premium) WordPress themes, plugins and services. We also provide news, reviews, guides and tutorials to help you build a premium WordPress website. Learn More.
Site Links WordPress Themes
WordPress Plugins
WordPress News
Guides & Tutorials
WordPress Hosting
Recent Posts
Content Curation & Social Voting WordPress Themes
Best Video WordPress Themes
